<driver id="driver/Postscript-Lexmark-black-only">
  <name>Postscript-Lexmark-black-only</name>
  <url>http://www.lexmark.com/</url>
  <supplier>Lexmark</supplier>
  <manufacturersupplied>Lexmark</manufacturersupplied>
  <license>Only verbatim redistribution</license>
  <licensetext>
    <en>

Copyright (c) 2004-2005 Lexmark International Inc.  All Rights Reserved.
Permission is granted for redistribution of this file as
long as this copyright notice is intact and the content
of the file is not altered in any way from its original form.

    </en>
  </licensetext>
  <nonfreesoftware />
  <shortdescription>
    <en>
      Manufacturer-supplied PPD files for Lexmark's black-only PostScript printers
    </en>
  </shortdescription>
  <packages>
    <package scope="general">openprinting-ppds-postscript-lexmark-black-only</package>
  </packages>
  <functionality>
    <monochrome />
    <text>100</text>
    <lineart>100</lineart>
    <graphics>100</graphics>
    <photo>100</photo>
  </functionality>
  <execution>
    <postscript />
  </execution>
  <comments>
    <en>

      Under this entry Lexmark's PPD files for their black-only
      PostScript printers are hosted. For these printers there is an
      extra driver entry as Lexmark did not support them any more at
      the time when they started to publish their PPDs under a free
      license.&lt;p&gt;

      PostScript printers are supported natively in Linux and Unix
      environments, so you only need the PPD file for your printer, no
      driver executables, to get access to all printing
      functionality. The PPD contains all information about properties
      and user-settable options which are specific to the printer and
      makes printing dialogs show these options and allow the user to
      control all the printer's functionality.&lt;p&gt;

      The PPDs only support the printing functionality of the
      printers. To use extra functionality, like scanning and faxing
      you will need additional drivers.&lt;p&gt;

      Note that these printers work, like all other PostScript
      printers, with &lt;a
      href=&quot;show_driver.cgi?driver=Postscript&quot;&gt;generic PostScript
      PPD files&lt;/a&gt;, but then you will not get access to all the
      printer specific functionality.&lt;p&gt;

    </en>
  </comments>
</driver>
